adultpaymaster.com 2011-01-02

# Adult Pay Master

## Privacy Policy

**I. Preamble and General Principles**

A. Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. 

B. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how TM Titan Media Solutions Ltd, d/b/a Adult Paymaster ("Adult Paymaster") collects information from all end users-those who access some of Adult Paymaster's Internet services (the "Services") but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who subscribe to the Services ("Affiliates")-what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Affiliates have concerning the collection and use of such information. Adult Paymaster requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**II. Revisions to this Policy**

Adult Paymaster reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check this web page for any modifications regarding this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user's browser. The user should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged, after the user has clicked the "refresh" button on his/her browser, the user may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the Policy. A changed "last modified" date indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting. 

**III. Personal Information Adult Paymaster Collects and How It Is Used**

A. Introduction. 

Adult Paymaster collects information in different ways from Visitors and Affiliates who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below. 

B. Registration. 

Affiliates are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, email address, Web site URL, messenger identification, Epassporte identification, tax identification or Social Security number, and wire information. The personal information collected from Affiliates during the registration process is used to manage each Affiliate's account. This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. However, in instances where Adult Paymaster and a partner jointly promote the Services, Adult Paymaster may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. Adult Paymaster may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Affiliates provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Affiliates). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services. 

C. Adult Paymaster Partners and Sponsors. 

Some Adult Paymaster products and services are offered to Visitors and Affiliates in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Affiliates some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature. Additionally, many Adult Paymaster Visitors and Affiliates have co-branded Personal Start Pages that are cosponsored by nonaffiliated partners. Adult Paymaster will share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered. 

D. Online Shopping. 

At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, and phone number. If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone number. Adult Paymaster has no control over the third parties' use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so. 

E. Online Advertisements. 

Adult Paymaster displays online advertisements. We share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Affiliates collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For instance, an advertiser tells us the audience they want to reach (for example, males between 25 and 55 years of age) and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to the intended audience. Adult Paymaster does not share personal information about its Visitors or Affiliates with these advertisers. 

F. Responses to Email Inquiries. 

When Visitors or Affiliates send email inquiries to Adult Paymaster the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Adult Paymaster does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

G. Voluntary Customer Surveys. 

1\. We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary. 

2\. We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our customer surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other Adult Paymaster customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties. 

3\. We also use our Visitors' and Affiliates' information for market research data purposes. For example, we may use your information in order to find ways to improve sales to a group of other users, to increase a user's experience according to the interests of the user, or to formulate statistical models to accomplish such goals through surveys or contests.

H. Other Internet Data. 

Adult Paymaster also collects IP addresses, referral URLs, browser preferences, Affiliate registration forms, surveys, and communications transmitted through site applications in order to collect information from Visitors and Affiliates of Adult Paymaster. This information is used internally for the purposes of providing additional personalized services to our Visitors and Affiliates. This information may be disclosed to third-parties. If we choose to disclose information to third-parties, this information shall consist of non-specific information regarding site traffic and statistics. Adult Paymaster never discloses any Visitor's or Affiliate's specific information to third parties unless it is compelled to by law, a Court Order, or other state, local, or administrative regulation. 

I. Special Cases. 

It is Adult Paymaster's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Affiliates in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, Adult Paymaster may disclose personal information about Visitors or Affiliates, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy, [Terms and Conditions](http://www.adultpaymaster.com/terms.php), Affiliate Agreement, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect Adult Paymaster and our Visitors and Affiliates. 

J. "Cookies" and How Adult Paymaster Uses Them. 

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Adult Paymaster may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you have registered for our Services, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-Adult Paymaster Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

K. Company Email. 

Adult Paymaster periodically sends email to its Affiliates. The only way for the Affiliate's email address to be added to our email list is for the Affiliate to provide this information to us. Adult Paymaster has an Opt-in Policy and an Opt-out Policy. If an Affiliate responds to the email requesting to be removed from Adult Paymaster's periodic mailing list, that Affiliate's request will be honored. Adult Paymaster takes all reasonable steps in order to adhere with this Policy. Nevertheless, Adult Paymaster is not responsible for occasional technical malfunctions which may result in additional unwanted emails being sent. Should this occur, the user (Affiliate) is instructed to direct an inquiry to Adult Paymaster's Customer Service email address, which is wmsupport@adultpaymaster.com. 

**IV. Our Commitment to Children's Protection.**

A. Our sites are designed for adults, but not for use by anyone under the age of 18. IN light of that fact, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 is not applicable to this site. 

B. We have no Web pages designed for younger users. We make every effort to ensure that our Web sites contain adequate warnings to make their content obvious and to warn users under the age of 18 that they are not welcome to view our Web sites, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision of their children's internet use. Nevertheless, we will take any steps possible to discourage those under the age of 18 from visiting our Web sites. For further information about tips, tools, age-appropriate, or kid-friendly Web sites and how to report online trouble, please visit www.getnetwise.org. 

**V. Adult Paymaster's Commitment to Data Security.**

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

**VII. How to Access or Modify Your Information.**

Adult Paymaster offers Affiliates the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, log in to your account and follow instructions to modify your account information or contact our Customer Service Department at wmsupport@adultpaymaster.com. 

**VIII. Where to Direct Questions about Adult Paymaster's Privacy Policy.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: 

Adult Paymaster's Customer Service Department: wmsupport@adultpaymaster.com 

**IX. Revisions to This Policy.**

Adult Paymaster reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check this web page for any modifications regarding this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user's browser. The user should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged, after the user has clicked the "refresh" button on his/her browser, the user may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" date indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting.
